<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bio</string>
    <string name="full_name">LE VAN TU</string>

    <string name="bio">
        Once upon a time in a small village, there lived a young boy named Jack.\n
        He was known for his insatiable curiosity and boundless love for adventures.\n\n

        One day, while rummaging through the dusty old attic of his house, Jack stumbled upon an ancient, weathered map.\n
        Excited beyond words, he rushed to show it to his best friend, Lucy.\n
        "This looks like a treasure map!" Lucy exclaimed, her eyes wide with amazement.\n\n

        The next morning, as the sun peeked over the horizon, Jack and Lucy packed their bags with essentials for their journey.\n
        With the map in hand, they set off on what would become the greatest adventure of their young lives.\n
        The map led them through dense forests where the sunlight barely pierced through the thick canopy,\n
        across raging rivers that tested their courage, and up steep, treacherous mountains.\n
        Each step of the way was filled with challenges that seemed insurmountable at first.\n
        They encountered ancient riddles that required their sharp wits to solve,\n
        escaped cleverly designed traps that had been set to deter intruders,\n
        and discovered hidden clues that guided them further on their quest.\n\n

        Days turned into nights as they braved the wilderness, their determination unwavering.\n
        After what felt like an eternity of traveling and overcoming obstacles, they finally reached a clearing.\n
        Before them lay the spot marked with a prominent \'X\' on the map.\n
        With hearts pounding in anticipation, they began to dig.\n
        The earth gave way, revealing an old wooden chest, its surface adorned with intricate carvings.\n
        As they pried it open, the sunlight caught the gleam of gold coins and precious jewels within.\n
        Their eyes sparkled with excitement and disbelief, for they had found the legendary treasure.\n\n

        Jack and Lucy returned to their village as heroes, their adventure becoming the talk of the town.\n
        They shared their newfound wealth with the villagers, ensuring that everyone benefited from their incredible journey.\n
        Their tale of courage, friendship, and discovery quickly became a legendary story,\n
        inspiring many young adventurers in the years to come to seek their own paths of wonder and exploration.\n\n

        The end.

    </string>
    <string name="enter_your_hobbies">Enter your hobbies</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>

</resources>
